Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur audiovisual material, 1994 -- 2006; 1995 -- 2001; MS148.002; 0.25 Linear Feet; 552 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - 109A: Bugged; 109B: Desperately seeking Stanley, 2003; MS148.002.174.00016 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files for Bugged can be found at MS148/001-023#00019-00022. Associated first cut for Bugged can be found at MS148/002-568#00001 and MS148/002-569#00001. Associated mix for approval for Bugged can be found at MS148/002-570#00001. Associated tapes for Bugged can be found at MS148/002-472#00002, MS148/002-473#00002, and MS148/002-474#00002. Associated production files for Desperately seeking Stanley can be found at MS148/001-023#00023-00025. Associated mix for approval for Desperately seeking Stanley can be found at MS148/002-570#00002. Associated tapes for Desperately seeking Stanley can be found at MS148/002-484#00002, MS148/002-485#00002, MS148/002-486#00002.
  - 110A: Bitzi's break-up; 110B: Fernkenstein's monster, 2003; MS148.002.174.00017 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files for Bitzi's break-up can be found at MS148/001-023#00026. Associated first cut for Bitzi's break-up can be found at MS148/002-571#00001. Associated mix for approval for Bitzi's break-up can be found at MS148/002-573#00001. Associated tapes for Bitzi's break-up can be found at MS148/002-466#00002, MS148/002-467#00002, and MS148/002-468#00002. Associated production files for Fernkenstein's monster can be found at MS148/001-023#00027. Associated first cut for Fernkenstein's monster can be found at MS148/002-572#00001. Associated mix for approval for Fernkenstein's monster can be found at MS148/002-573#00001. Associated tapes for Fernkenstein's monster can be found at MS148/002-475#00001, MS148/002-476#00001, and MS148/002-477#00001.
  - 111A: Sue Ellen chicken's out; 111B: Vomitrocious!, 2003; MS148.002.174.00018 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00028-00033.
  - 112A: Postcards from Buster, part I; 112B: Desk wars, 2003; MS148.002.174.00019 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files for Postcards from Buster, part I can be found at MS148/001-023#00034-00036. Associated first cut for Postcards from Buster, part I can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated mix for approval for Postcards from Buster, part I can be found at MS148/002-192#00001 and MS148/002-193#00001. Associated tapes for Postcards from Buster, part I can be found at MS148/002-481#00001, MS148/002-482#00001, MS148/002-483#00001, MS148/002-526#00001, and MS148/002-527#00001. Associated production files for Desk wars can be found at MS148/001-023#00037-00039. Associated first cut for Desk wars can be found at MS148/002-574#00002. Associated mix for approval for Desk wars can be found at MS148/002-192#00002 and MS148/002-193#00002. Associated tapes for Desk wars can be found at MS148/002-484#00001, MS148/002-485#00001, and MS148/002-486#00001.
  - 115B: Big horns George, 2003-05-14; MS148.002.174.00020 (Case 174)
    Songs. Line 23--Brain; Line 44--George; Line 75-80--George; Line 101--Hi pitch George; Line 101--Lo pitch George; Lines 112-120--Hi pitch (George, Koko and guide) short; Lines 112-120--Hi pitch (George, Koko and guide) long; Lines 112-120--Lo pitch (George, Koko and guide). Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00001-00003.
  - 116A: Castles in the sky; 116B: George blows his top, 2003; MS148.002.174.00021 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00004-00006. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-575#00001.
  - 117A: My fair Tommy; 117B: Francine's big top trouble, 2004-06-11; MS148.002.174.00022 (Case 174)
    Color for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00007-00012.
  - 118A: The law of the jungle gym; 118B: All worked up, 2004-06-22; MS148.002.174.00023 (Case 174)
    Color for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00013-00015.
  - 119A: Tipping the scales; 119B: Lights, camera...opera!, 2003; MS148.002.174.00024 (Case 174)
    Color. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00016-00021.
  - 120A: Arthur weighs in; 120B: Buster's green thumb, 2004-07-21; MS148.002.175.00001 (Case 175)
    Color for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00022-00023.
  - 121A: "A" is for angry; 121B: Emily swallows a horse, 2004-08-20; MS148.002.175.00002 (Case 175)
    Color. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00024-00025.
  - 123A: Arthur makes waves; 123B: Three's a crowd, 2004-09-15; MS148.002.175.00003 (Case 175)
    Color. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00026.
  - 124A: D.W. beats all; 124B: It came from beyond, 2004-09-28; MS148.002.175.00004 (Case 175)
    Color for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00027.
  - 125A: The "A" team; 125B: Buster the myth maker, 2004; MS148.002.175.00005 (Case 175)
    Color for approval. No associated production files.
  - 126A: Desert island dish; 126B: Feeling flush, 2004; MS148.002.175.00006; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    Aspect ratio: 1.33, NTSC+TCBI, English. No associated production files.
    DVD
  - 126A: Desert island dish; 126B: Feeling flush, 2005-10-26; MS148.002.175.00007 (Case 175)
    Offline, first cut. No associated production files.
  - 127A: Flaw and order; 127B: Fern and Persimmony Glitchet, 2005-11-10; MS148.002.175.00008 (Case 175)
    TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 127A: Flaw and order; 127B: Fern and Persimmony Glitchet, 2005; MS148.002.175.00009; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 128A: The squirrels; 128B: Arthur changes gears, 2005-11-24; MS148.002.175.00010; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    Rough cut, TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 128A: The squirrels; 128B: Arthur changes gears, 2005; MS148.002.175.00011; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 129A: Buster's special delivery; 129B: What's cooking, 2005-12-07; MS148.002.175.00012 (Case 175)
    Offline, first cut for approval, TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 129A: Buster's special delivery; 129B: What's cooking, 2005; MS148.002.175.00013; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 130A: D.W. aims high; 130B: Family fortune, 2005; MS148.002.175.00014; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 130A: D.W. aims high; 130B: Family fortune, 2005-12-22; MS148.002.175.00015; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 131A: D.W. bossy boots; 131B: Unfinished, 2005; MS148.002.175.00016; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 131A: D.W. bossy boots; 131B: Unfinished, 2006-01-11; MS148.002.175.00017; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    First cut for approval, TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 132A: Happy Anniversary, pt. I; 132B: World girls, 2006-02-23; MS148.002.175.00018; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    Mix for approval, TC burn-in, English full mix. No associated production files.
  - 132A: Happy Anniversary, pt. I; 132B: World girls, 2006-01-25; MS148.002.175.00019; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 133A: The secret about secrets; 133B: Happy Anniversary, pt. II, 2006-02-09; MS148.002.175.00020; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 133A: The secret about secrets; 133B: Happy Anniversary, pt. II, 2006-03-08; MS148.002.175.00021; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    Mix for approval, TCBI, English full mix. No associated production files.
  - 134A: Operation: D.W.!; 134B: Binky vs. Binky, 2006-02-23; MS148.002.175.00022 (Case 175)
  - 134A: Operation: D.W.!; 134B: Binky vs. Binky, 2006-03-23; MS148.002.175.00023; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    For content approval, TCBI, English full mix. No associated production files.
  - 134A: Operation: D.W.!; 134B: Binky vs. Binky, 2006-03-23; MS148.002.175.00024; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 134A: Operation: D.W.!; 134B: Binky vs. Binky, 2006-03-03; MS148.002.175.00025; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
    Music for approval, TCBI. No associated production files.
  - 135A: The curse of the Grebes; 135B: Do you speak George?, 2006-03-08; MS148.002.175.00026; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 135A: The curse of the Grebes; 135B: Do you speak George?, 2006-03-31; MS148.002.175.00027; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Case 175)
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, 2001-07-24; MS148.002.176.00001; Cinar (Box 176)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00001-00004. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-552#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00001, MS148/002-418#00001, and MS148/002-419#00001.
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, 2001-07-24; MS148.002.176.00002; Cinar (Box 176)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00005-00008. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-552#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-420#00001 and MS148/002-421#00001.
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, 2001-08-07; MS148.002.177.00001; Cinar (Box 177)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00018-00022. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-553#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00002, MS148/002-418#00002, and MS148/002-419#00002.
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, 2001-08-07; MS148.002.177.00002; Cinar (Box 177)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00023-00027. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-553#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-414#00001, MS148/002-415#00001, and MS148/002-416#00001.
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, 2001-07-27; MS148.002.178.00001; Cinar (Box 178)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00028-00032.
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, 2001-07-27; MS148.002.178.00002; Cinar (Box 178)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00033-00038.
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, 2001-09-05; MS148.002.179.00001; Cinar (Box 179)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00039-00040, MS148/001-021#00001-00004, and MS148/001-021#00010-00011 Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-425#00001, MS148/002-426#00001, and MS148/002-427#00001.
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, 2001-09-05; MS148.002.179.00002; Cinar (Box 179)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00005-00010. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-422#00001, MS148/002-423#00001, and MS148/002-424#00001.
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, 2001-09-18; MS148.002.180.00001; Cinar (Box 180)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00011-00015.
  - 93B: More!, 2001-09-18; MS148.002.180.00002; Cinar (Box 180)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00010, 00016-00019.
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, 2001-09-07; MS148.002.181.00001; Cinar (Box 181)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00020-00024.
  - 94B: The good sport, 2001-09-07; MS148.002.181.00002; Cinar (Box 181)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00025-00028.
  - 95A: Crushed, 2001; MS148.002.182.00001; Cinar (Box 182)
    This date is approximate. First cut, client's copy. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00029-00032.
  - 95B: Arthur loses his marbles, 2001; MS148.002.182.00002; Cinar (Box 182)
    This date is approximate. First cut, client's copy. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00033-00036.
  - 95A: Crushed, 2001-10-16; MS148.002.183.00001; Cinar (Box 183)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00029-00032.
  - 95B: Arthur loses his marbles, 2001-10-16; MS148.002.183.00002; Cinar (Box 183)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00033-00036.
  - It's only rock 'n' roll, starring the Backstreet Boys, 2002-05-23; MS148.002.184.00001; Cinar (Box 184)
    First cut, client copy, 2 min 30 sec, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00020-00047. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-525#00001. Associated NTSC/Stereo tape can be found at MS158/002-551. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00006-00008.
  - 103A: Jenna's bedtime blues, 2002-09-18; MS148.002.185.00001; Cinar (Box 185)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00069-00072. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-561#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-452#00002, MS148/002-453#00002, and MS148/002-454#00002. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00012.
  - 103B: Prunella sees the light, 2002-09-18; MS148.002.185.00002; Cinar (Box 185)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00073-00077. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-562#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-461#00001, MS148/002-462#00001, and MS148/002-463#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00012.
  - 104A: The world of tomorrow, 2002-10-02; MS148.002.186.00001; Cinar (Box 186)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00077-00079.
  - 104B: Return of the snowball, 2002-10-02; MS148.002.186.00002; Cinar (Box 186)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, ful stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00080.
  - 104A: The world of tomorrow, 2002-09-06; MS148.002.187.00001; Cinar (Box 187)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00077-00079.
  - 104B: Return of the snowball, 2002-09-06; MS148.002.187.00002; Cinar (Box 187)
    First cut, clients. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-022#00080.
  - 105A: April 9th, part I, 2002-10-16; MS148.002.188.00001; Cinar (Box 188)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00002-00004.
  - 105B: April 9th, part II, 2002-10-16; MS148.002.188.00002; Cinar (Box 188)
    Mix for approval, tr1-2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00005-00007.
  - 105A: April 9th, part I, 2002-09-23; MS148.002.189.00001; Cinar (Box 189)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00002-00004.
  - 105B: April 9th, part II, 2002-09-23; MS148.002.189.00002; Cinar (Box 189)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00005-00007.
  - 106A: Arthur's snow biz, 2003-05-21; MS148.002.190.00001; Cinar (Box 190)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00008-00009. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/001-563#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-472#00001, MS148/002-473#00001, and MS148/002-474#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00013.
  - 106B: Dear Adil, 2003-05-21; MS148.002.190.00002; Cinar (Box 190)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00010. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/001-563#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-466#00001, MS148/002-467#00001, and MS148/002-468#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00013.
  - 107A: Thanks a lot, Binky, 2003-06-03; MS148.002.191.00001; Cinar (Box 191)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00011. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/001-564#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-469#00002, MS148/002-470#00002, and MS148/002-471#00002. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00014.
  - 107B: D.W., dancing queen, 2003-06-03; MS148.002.191.00002; Cinar (Box 191)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00012. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/001-564#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-475#00002, MS148/002-476#00002, and MS148/002-477#00002. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00014.
  - 112A: Postcards from Buster, part I, 2003-09-03; MS148.002.192.00001; Cinar (Box 192)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00034-00036. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-193#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-481#00001, MS148/002-482#00001, MS148/002-483#00001, MS148/002-526#00001, and MS148/002-527#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 112B: Desk wars, 2003-09-03; MS148.002.192.00002; Cinar (Box 192)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00037-00039. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-193#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-484#00001, MS148/002-485#00001, and MS148/002-486#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 112A: Postcards from Buster, part I, 2003-09-16; MS148.002.193.00001; Cinar (Box 193)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00034-00036. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-192#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-481#00001, MS148/002-482#00001, MS148/002-483#00001, MS148/002-526#00001, and MS148/002-527#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 112B: Desk wars, 2003-09-16; MS148.002.193.00002; Cinar (Box 193)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00037-00039. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-574#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-192#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-484#00001, MS148/002-485#00001, and MS148/002-486#00001. Associated CD can be found at MS148/002-174#00019.
  - 113A: Tales from the crib, 2003-09-16; MS148.002.193.00003; Cinar (Box 193)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00040-00042.
  - 113B: Postcards from Buster, part II, 2003-09-16; MS148.002.193.00004; Cinar (Box 193)
    Mix for approval, ch1-ch2, full stereo mix, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00043-00045.
  - 113A: Tales from the crib, 2003-09-16; MS148.002.194.00001; Cinar (Box 194)
  - 113A: Tales from the crib, 2003-08-22; MS148.002.195.00001; Cinar (Box 195)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00040-00042.
  - 113B: Postcards from Buster, part II, 2003-08-22; MS148.002.196.00001; Cinar (Box 196)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00043-00045.
  - 114A: Muffy's art attack, 2003-08-30; MS148.002.197.00001; Cinar (Box 197)
    Mix for approval, full mix, ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00046-00048.
  - 114B: Flea to be you and me, 2003-08-30; MS148.002.197.00002; Cinar (Box 197)
    Mix for approval, full mix, ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00049-00051.
  - 114A: Muffy's art attack, 2003-09-05; MS148.002.198.00001; Cinar (Box 198)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files include MS148/001-023#00046-00048.
  - 114B: Flea to be you and me, 2003-09-05; MS148.002.199.00001; Cinar (Box 199)
    First cut, client's copy. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00049-00051.
  - 115A: Kiss and tell, 2003-10-15; MS148.002.200.00001; Cinar (Box 200)
    Mix for approval, full mix ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00052-00054.
  - 115B: Big horns George, 2003-10-15; MS148.002.200.00002; Cinar (Box 200)
    Mix for approval, full mix, ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00001.
  - 115A: Kiss and tell, 2003-09-23; MS148.002.201.00001; Cinar (Box 201)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-023#00052-00054.
  - 115B: Big horns George, 2003-09-24; MS148.002.202.00001; Cinar (Box 202)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00001.
  - 117A: My fair Tommy, 2004-09-21; MS148.002.203.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 203)
    Mix for approval, copy, TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00004-00006.
  - 117B: Francine's big top trouble, 2004-09-21; MS148.002.203.00002; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 203)
    Mix for approval, copie TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00007-00009.
  - 118A: The law of the jungle gym, 2004-09-15; MS148.002.204.00001; Cinar (Box 204)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00010.
  - 118B: All worked up, 2004-09-15; MS148.002.204.00002; Cinar (Box 204)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00011-00012.
  - 118A: The law of the jungle gym, 2004-10-12; MS148.002.205.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 205)
    Mix for approval, TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00010.
  - 118B: All worked up, 2004-10-12; MS148.002.205.00002; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 205)
    Mix for approval, TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00011-00012.
  - 119A: Tipping the scales, 2004-09-23; MS148.002.206.00001; Cinar (Box 206)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00013-00015.
  - 119B: Lights, camera...opera!, 2004-09-23; MS148.002.206.00002; Cinar (Box 206)
    First cut, client copy, audio ch1, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00016-00018.
  - 119A: Tipping the scales, 2004-10-19; MS148.002.207.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 207)
    Mix for approval, copie TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00013-00015.
  - 119B: Lights, camera...opera!, 2004-10-19; MS148.002.207.00002; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 207)
    Mix for approval, copie TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00016-00018.
  - 120A: Arthur weighs in, 2004-11-09; MS148.002.208.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 208)
    Mix for approval, copie TCBI. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-024#00019.
  - 120B: Buster's green thumb, 2004-11-09; MS148.002.208.00002; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 208)